Prologue: Beyond Memories

Early one morning, in the spirit folk village...

In the house where Miharu was living together with Latifa and the others, Miharu was sleeping alone in her room. However, from the look on her face, she seemed to be having a bad dream.

“H-Haru-kun?!” After a moment, she let out a frantic yell and moved her hands as though to hug someone, but the person she was trying to hug wasn’t there.

...What was I doing? Miharu returned to her senses with a gasp and looked around the room, confirming where she was. It was a familiar room — the room she had been sleeping in every day since coming to the village.

Was I... dreaming?

Right... it was a dream. She recalled seeing a dream. A very sad dream...

...I can’t remember it. Miharu frowned in frustration. It was an extremely important dream, wasn’t it? Someone had been in pain... That’s why Miharu had tried so desperately to hug the person in the dream. She knew she couldn’t be separated from them, because, if she were, that person would go somewhere far away.

“I have to remember...” Spurred on by a vague compulsion, Miharu desperately tried to remember the dream she had just moments ago. It wasn’t too late to recall something yet. There should still be something there, somewhere...

“...Haruto?” At the back of Miharu’s mind, the faint image of Rio holding a sword from behind resurfaced. Rio was watching something with an extremely stern expression in the dream. He glared at someone, before swinging his sword down on them... perhaps.

But upon further consideration, hadn’t Miharu said the name of a different person when she woke up? The nickname of the boy she was always with when she was young...

“Haru... kun?” Miharu whispered softly. The nickname of her childhood friend, Amakawa Haruto...

Was that a dream... about Haru-kun? Miharu frowned sadly at the doubt she felt. Then, she suddenly recalled her past with Haruto and clenched her fist around her nightgown.

Back in those days, Miharu had thought it was only natural to be with Haruto. It was a given that she would grow older with Haruto, and those days they spent together would continue forever naturally. She had been seven years old when she learned that it wasn’t meant to be — nine years ago. It was why Miharu could remember those days she spent with Haruto so clearly, it was as though they had only happened yesterday. Because Miharu liked Haruto — because Miharu loved Haruto, she was devastated to be separated from such an important person. It was so painful that she would never forget it.

She still remembered the promise they made when they parted, too. There was no binding power at all behind it — a fleeting promise between two children. Her feelings now could be different from love, but even so, that promise was still something sacred to her.

That’s why Miharu would occasionally remember Haruto, even though she had grown older. While she felt very sad that Aki had nothing but prejudice towards Haruto, every time Miharu remembered him, she felt warmth in her chest that supported her, as though he was beside her.

She wondered how Haruto had grown up. Did he still remember the promise like she did? If he did, and they were ever to reunite like they promised, what would they do? Miharu thought about those things every time she remembered Haruto.

The answer was the same every time: it was possible she would fall in love with Haruto once more. It’d be a wonderful thing if that happened, she thought. But recently, whenever Miharu remembered Haruto, she found her chest tightening in pain instead. And she knew the reason why: it had started after she began living in this world with Haruto.

Haruto and Haruto. Their identical names could be part of it, but Miharu occasionally found herself feeling a sense of déjà vu as she went about her days living with him. She had started overlapping the two — Haruto, and Amakawa Haruto.

Miharu wasn’t very good at interacting with the opposite gender to begin with. She was fine with the younger Masato since he was still a child, but she sometimes found herself in an awkward silence around Aki’s older stepbrother, Takahisa. That was why the only same-aged boy Miharu could spend time with without any objection was Haruto, who she had grown up with from a young age.

Until she came to this world and met Haruto, that is...

For some reason, from the moment she had met the Haruto in this world, she had never felt nervous around him. It made Haruto one of the few people Miharu could interact with without feeling particularly uncomfortable. If she didn’t count Haruto from her childhood, then he might’ve been the first.

The reason she felt so comfortable around him was because the feeling that Haruto and Amakawa Haruto gave off was similar. She wasn’t able to explain it in detail, but the feeling of reassurance when they were together was the same. Miharu started to realize that as she spent more time with Haruto, and before she knew it, she was overlapping Haruto with Amakawa Haruto.

However, she didn’t think that was necessarily a good thing, as it was rude to compare someone with someone else like that. It was a feeling Miharu had hidden in her heart... until she heard the story of when Rio first visited the village from Orphia and Alma.

According to Orphia and Alma, Rio had muttered “Mii-chan” when he’d been unconscious in a cell. It was the nickname that Haruto had once called Miharu by. Of course, it could’ve been a coincidence, and there may have been nothing behind his sleep talking; not to mention the fact that Haruto had previously said he died a university student. Even so, Miharu couldn’t help the seed of suspicion growing within her. It was possible Haruto’s previous life was as Amakawa Haruto.

That couldn’t be, Miharu said to herself, but the suspicion remained.

I can only remember it vaguely, but the person in my dream looked like Haruto... Miharu’s instincts were telling her the dream was about Haruto. As though insisting that the two men were the same.

“Then...” Miharu whispered quietly. “Does that mean Haruto is Haru-kun...?”

Her anxious voice echoed softly in the quiet room.

Chapter 2: Return

Meanwhile, a few moments earlier... The eastern skies welcomed daybreak as light reached the western skies and the ground below.

“Ah...!” The people present in Liselotte’s garden were all looking up at the sky in a daze. There, soaring through the skies was the black dragon-like creature Liselotte’s party had witnessed just the other day. Its mouth was open as it breathed a jet-black flame down at the city walls towards Amande’s northwest area.

However, the breath did not reach the ground. It collided with a single beam of light that stretched up from the ground and competed for dominance. In the next moment, the jet-black breath was pushed back, and a blinding flash of light tore across the sky.

Pretty... Liselotte vaguely thought about how beautiful the scene was. It was probably a magic of the highest grade, packed with tremendous destructive power, yet she couldn’t help but feel captivated by its beauty. Next to Liselotte, Celia was also looking at the sky in awe.

“...It’s retreating,” she mumbled quietly. The black dragon-like creature swiftly evaded the light that pushed back its breath, proceeding to change directions and fly away. Those in the estate garden watched on, astonished. After some time had passed, Aishia approached Celia with light footsteps.

“I’m done here, too. You can cancel your magic now,” she said in a casual tone, as though she had returned from a stroll. The revenants that had overrun the estate garden mere moments ago were all eliminated, leaving no trace behind. It really was nothing more than a walk in the park for Aishia.

“O-Okay. You’ve worked hard.” Celia deactivated the Magicae Murum barrier she had maintained until now and looked at Aishia as though she wanted to ask something.

“Haruto is fine,” Aishia informed her shortly, having guessed her thoughts. At that, Celia’s expression loosened slightly. Hearing Rio was safe from Aishia’s own mouth lightened the burden on her chest a little. She couldn’t ask for details in front of Liselotte, but she would believe in Aishia’s words.

“O-Oh,” Celia stammered in a light tone.

“...Thank you so much, to the both of you. Your assistance has helped minimize the damage that could’ve taken place here. I am truly grateful from the bottom of my heart.” Liselotte bowed her head to Aishia and Celia.

“N-No, I didn’t do anything useful. It was all thanks to Aishia.” Celia shook her head in a fluster, looking at Aishia.

“I only fought for Haruto’s sake. The situation still isn’t resolved, so we should consider what happens next,” Aishia said, looking around the estate. Thanks to Aishia’s participation and the fact the revenants were toying with the knights while fighting, the damage wasn’t as great as it could have been, but there were still casualties. Some of the knights among them were unconscious, so it was too early to think optimistically. There was also the possibility of fights breaking out elsewhere, outside of the estate grounds, too.

“...Of course.” Liselotte focused her expression into a serious one.

“Please pay us no heed and return to your post, Lady Liselotte. If you need an extra healer, I am able to use Cura and can lend a hand,” Celia said, urging Liselotte to take action.

“I’m sorry for putting you in this position. Could you please accompany me, then? I must confirm the situation with haste,” Liselotte requested with a bow of her head.

Cura users were few and far between. The effectiveness of recovery varied between users, but Celia’s use of magic in the earlier battle was of a rather high skill. There was much to be expected.

“Yes,” Celia agreed immediately. There was a high probability she knew the people inside, and though she was currently in hiding from the world, there was no way she could turn a blind eye with lives at stake.

“Follow me, then.”

Thus, Celia and Aishia accompanied Liselotte inside the mansion.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, in the living room inside the mansion, Roanna was healing Duke Huguenot. She used her healing magic to treat his abdomen, which had been punched by the Alphonse revenant.

“Guh... What’s happening... outside...?” Duke Huguenot asked, his face distorted from the pain in his torso. His mouth was stained red with blood he had spat out.

“Please refrain from speaking. Your internal organs are difficult enough to heal already,” Roanna scolded the stretched out Duke Huguenot with a serious expression. Squatted right beside her was Stewart, who was watching the treatment go on with a terribly panicked face.

“Lady Roanna, Father... Father will be all right, won’t he?!” Stewart asked in disarray.

“Calm down. The healing will take time, but there should be no fear for his life,” Roanna answered bluntly.

“...Okay,” Stewart fidgeted restlessly and nodded.

I don’t know why he passed out, but Sir Hiroaki is safe. But I worry for what happened to Princess Flora, who escaped outside... Even as Roanna devoted herself to healing Duke Huguenot, she worried for the safety and whereabouts of Flora. While there was no mistaking the fact that remaining in the room at that point was dangerous, she knew revenants had appeared outside soon after. She couldn’t help but worry.

“Has the knight who went out with the message still not returned?” Roanna asked in frustration and looked outside the door.

“He has just returned with Lady Liselotte, my lady!” the knight on guard outside the door replied. A short while later, Liselotte appeared alongside the messenger knight. Beside her were two attendants, as well as Celia and Aishia.

“Ugh...” The newcomers looked at the disaster around the room with solemn faces. There was a great hole opened in the wall of the hallway, and the interior was a battletorn mess. Laid to rest in the corner of the room were the corpses of the two knights that had been guarding the door before the attack.

Celia had a solemn face too, but when she noticed Duke Huguenot and her former students Roanna and Stewart, she readjusted her hood lower in a casual manner.

“...You two heal the wounded knights,” Liselotte ordered her two accompanying attendants, thinking it best to begin treatment on the knights that appeared to be less wounded.

“Yes, my lady!” The two attendants nodded, promptly taking action.

“May I ask what happened here?” Liselotte approached the wounded Duke Huguenot lying down and looked at the idle people for confirmation.

“M-Monsters came in! Humanoid ones! What was the mansion security doing?! My father was injured because of this!” Stewart cried out, scolding Liselotte in agitation.

“I apologize for my delay in noticing the monster’s attack...” Liselotte apologized with a shamed expression.

“S-Stop that, Stewart,” Duke Huguenot said with a grimace. “Roanna, you explain in his place.”

A bitter expression rose on Stewart’s face.

“Then I shall heal in her place.” Celia immediately walked over to Roanna and swapped out her healing duty.

“And you are...?” Roanna looked at Celia with her face hidden under the hood and tilted her head curiously.

“A helper. Report to Lady Liselotte first,” Celia said before placing her hand over Duke Huguenot’s wound and chanting the spell “Cura.”

“A swarm of humanoid monsters came surging into this room. We somehow managed to make it through thanks to Sir Hiroaki’s efforts, but Duke Huguenot was wounded severely...” Roanna reported on the situation with a small breath.

“...Is the hero safe?” Liselotte looked at Hiroaki and asked nervously. Hiroaki had been laid on the floor, still unconscious.

“Yes, after he drove away the monsters he suddenly passed out, but there’s no particular danger to his life. Also, if I may ask — where is Princess Flora? We managed to get her away from the room, but...” Roanna asked in a panic.

“I’d like you to listen to this calmly...” Liselotte began, looking at Roanna.

“...Please, tell me.” Roanna had a bad feeling, but urged her to continue.

Liselotte gritted her teeth and stated the truth bluntly. “Princess Flora has been kidnapped by someone.”

“W-What did you say?! Why... How? How could that happen?!” Sure enough, Roanna was extremely upset.

“The details are unclear. When the monsters were rushing into the garden, a strange man came running out of the mansion with Princess Flora and escaped outside of the grounds in the chaos.”

“N-No...” Roanna looked like the end of the world had come as she sank to her knees weakly. “...Sir Haruto is currently pursuing the man alone, but we cannot afford to sit idly in the meantime, either. First, there is still the possibility that the man’s accomplices are in the area, so could you tell me the events that took place when Princess Flora was taken out of the room?” There may be a clue there, Liselotte thought as she asked, but Roanna was white as a sheet from the shock.

“I heard a gentleman’s voice in the confusion when the humanoid monsters were swarming into the room, s-so I told her to... I can’t believe that man was... W-What h-have I done...” Roanna said in a trembling voice. In all probability, that man must have been the culprit that took Flora, which left Roanna feeling like she had the responsibility for entrusting Flora to him.

“...There’s no point in worrying about what has been done. The only thing we can do now is believe in Sir Haruto. Your judgment was the correct one in that situation, Roanna. Liselotte, you too. The situation here is being handled. You should return to giving directions to everyone else,” Duke Huguenot said with an ashen face.

“A-Are you really all right, Duke Huguenot? Please don’t push yourself...” Liselotte asked in a fluster.

“No, I can tell the pain has lessened from before. It’s all thanks to your wonderful skill,” Duke Huguenot said, looking up at Celia as she used her healing magic.

Celia looked at Roanna from under her hood. “...No, my lady over there had already completed all the preliminary treatment with her Cura. All I did was continue that. Once the finishing touches have been applied, you should be good,” she said humbly. She was a little scared that her former students, Roanna and Stewart, would recognize her from her voice, but the two of them seemed to be preoccupied with other things at the moment.

“F-Father! You have recovered!” Stewart brightened with a smile when he saw Duke Huguenot’s complexion return to normal.

“...” Duke Huguenot averted his eyes from Stewart awkwardly. The difference in enthusiasm between the two showed their warped father-child relationship.

“Then I shall excuse myself for now. Sir Haruto may return at some point, so Lady Cecilia and Lady Aishia should come with me. Grace, you continue with Duke Huguenot’s treatment. I’m leaving this place to the rest of you,” Liselotte said.

“Understood. Please leave this to me, Lady Cecilia,” Grace requested respectfully, approaching Celia to heal Duke Huguenot.

“Thank you.” Celia removed her hand from the wound and passed the task on to Grace.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, Rio was carrying Flora in his arms as he ran along the rooftops of the noble district at the northwest of the city. His destination was, of course, Liselotte’s estate.

“...” Flora stared intensely up at Rio’s face from close range. However, Rio didn’t say anything despite noticing Flora’s gaze.

Sir... Haruto... So close, yet so far. It made Flora feel so sad. She grasped at Rio’s clothes tightly.

At that, Rio landed on the ramparts surrounding the noble district in the inner city and paused for a moment.

“The mansion is in view now.”

“Yes,” Flora whispered with a near inaudible voice.

“...Are you feeling unwell, by any chance? I held back as much as I could, but all that leaping must have shaken you up and down a lot. If you’re feeling a bit of motion sickness, you can rest here for a moment.” While Rio had a guess as to why Flora was being gloomy, he chose to offer another excuse out of consideration.

“N-No, I’m fine.” Flora shook her head quickly; she wasn’t feeling bad because of the motion. Rio’s consideration had been seemingly off, but he had purposefully acted considerately in the wrong way. The murky feelings within Flora grew larger when she suspected that.

“Then, let’s hurry. I’m sure everyone is worried too,” Rio said calmly before leaping once more. This time, Rio’s body floated lightly in the air, as though his feet had sprouted wings. He landed like that on the roof of a nearby building.

Hop, float, hop, float. Flora felt like she was a flower petal dancing in the wind. Her body felt light, but her heart felt as though it was heavy and being swallowed by the ground below.

The short but endless silence resumed between them, and the two of them arrived at the mansion roughly a minute later.

◇　◇　◇

Rio leaped over the estate walls he had crossed once in his pursuit of Lucius and returned to Liselotte’s estate grounds. With Flora still in his arms in a princess carry, he headed towards the garden of the estate at a walking pace.

“Haruto!” Celia noticed Rio’s presence first and came running over in a hurry. Aishia was right beside her, so they probably knew he was approaching in advance.

Rio smiled gently in response to Celia and Aishia. “Sorry for worrying the two of you.”

“It’s okay. Princess Flora, I’m glad you’re safe,” Celia said awkwardly, looking at Flora. She noticed that Flora’s complexion was off, but she couldn’t help but feel uncomfortable at the novel sight of Rio holding Flora in a princess carry. It was something she never would have imagined during their academy days.

“Yes. You’re...” Flora looked at the hood-covered Celia and tilted her head in question. Just then, Liselotte noticed Rio’s return and came running.

“Sir Haruto! Princess Flora! The two of you are safe!” Liselotte called out excitedly. Her expression was one of utmost relief, as though all of her worries had been eased.

“I have brought Princess Flora back as promised. Unfortunately, the kidnapper managed to get away...” Rio said with a bitter expression once Liselotte ran over.

“Not to worry! I can’t thank you enough for bringing Princess Flora back,” Liselotte vehemently denied his words. The situation had been on the brink of utter despair, but they somehow managed to avoid the worst possible outcome with this. Just having Flora return unharmed was the most fortuitous stroke of luck she could have asked for.

“Then, may I leave Princess Flora to you?” Having completed his duty, Rio wanted to entrust Flora’s safety to Liselotte.

“Of course. For now, let us move inside the mansion. You can tell me the details on the way,” said Liselotte.

“Understood. Then, Princess Flora, I’ll let you down here,” Rio said, moving to set Flora to the ground. However, Flora suddenly grabbed at Rio’s clothes in clear refusal to get down on the ground. Celia and Liselotte both looked wide-eyed at Flora with surprised expressions.

“U-Umm, my legs still feel numb... I’m sorry.” Flora realized she had done something awkward and made an uncomfortable face, explaining herself with a barely audible voice.

“...I understand. Then if it isn’t too presumptuous of me, I shall escort you to the mansion like this,” Rio stated without batting an eye.

“Thank you for your assistance, Sir Haruto.” Liselotte bowed her head apologetically to Rio. She had the mistaken idea that Flora was still frightened from being kidnapped.

Celia had the same thought as Liselotte and spoke to Rio softly, “Umm, thank you, Haruto.”

“Yes, of course.” Rio turned a gentle smile to Celia and walked forward immediately.

“Uh...” When Flora witnessed the smile Rio directed at Celia, she frowned at the difference in treatment she could feel compared to herself, but Celia and Liselotte began walking along with them to the mansion none the wiser. For the record, most of Liselotte’s attendant girls were occupied by the cleanup efforts after all the commotion inside and outside the mansion, inevitably leaving Liselotte the role of guiding them to the mansion.

Liselotte explained the situation to an attendant nearby before inviting Rio and the others to follow her. “Now, Sir Haruto. There’s just one thing to address before I ask you about the kidnapper. Earlier, a black dragon-like creature near the northwest area released a breath. The one who forced that breath back was...”

“...It was me. I don’t know whether it was coincidental or not, but just as the kidnapper was pushed back into a corner, that breath came down. I used my enchanted sword to counter it immediately, but the culprit got away...” Rio’s face stiffened and he spoke in a flat tone.

“So it was you...” Liselotte must have expected that, as she didn’t seem all that surprised at his reply. That being said, there were many thoughts she had about it...

“I have an idea of the kidnapper’s background. Rather, I knew of the man in question... The moment he appeared in the garden, I realized I had heard that voice before. That’s why I tried to chase after him. Of course, with the intention to rescue Princess Flora as well.” Rio didn’t go too deep into the irregular and unpredictable actions of the dragon-like creature, but spoke of Lucius instead.

“Is that... true?” Celia asked Rio in a daze.

“...Yes,” Rio confirmed, ashamed.

“Do you know the man’s name?” Liselotte asked nervously.

“Yes. The man’s name is Lucius. I believe him to be the same person as the leader of the mercenary squad, The Heavenly Lions — also known as The Griffins,” Rio revealed in a sharp tone.

By gathering information in the Strahl region whenever possible, Rio had learned that Lucius was the name of the man that led The Griffins. He also found that descriptions of that man’s appearance aligned with what Rio knew of Lucius as well.

“I’ve heard of that. It’s the veteran mercenary squad comprised of a small number of elite warriors, right? They haven’t shown themselves in public recently, so there were rumors they had disbanded...” Liselotte nodded in contemplation.

“You’re as knowledgeable as I expected,” Rio said, turning to her.

“That’s how renowned The Griffins are in this line of business, so it was more like necessary knowledge for me... But how did you know that man, Sir Haruto?” Liselotte asked while examining Rio’s expression.

“...He’s someone I have a bit of a past with,” Rio answered evasively, an awkward look on his face.

...Someone Rio has a past with? Celia cocked her head and looked at Rio curiously. As far as pasts went, Rio had attended the royal academy from age seven to twelve. He shouldn’t have had many opportunities to interact with the outside world, either. This meant that this man named Lucius must have had something to do with Rio either before he turned seven, or after he left the academy.

However, contrary to Celia’s pondering, Flora — who had been listening to the words exchanged in the earlier battle — had a very sad face.

Liselotte read the situation and apologized in shame. “Forgive me, I have pried too far in my questioning.”

Rio dismissed this and changed the topic to the core of the matter. “Not at all. But the more important question here should be which force is trying to kidnap Princess Flora, would you agree? Both the appearance of the monsters and dragon-like creature was timed too conveniently for the series of events that occurred.”

“...I’ve never heard of a technique that could control monsters, so I do admit I am curious. By force, do you think that someone has hired this mercenary named Lucius?”

“Yes. During his escape, another man assisted Lucius. His name was Reiss.”

“Reiss...”

“Does it ring a bell?” Rio asked.

“...No,” Liselotte shook her head.

“While he managed to get away, Lucius suffered heavy wounds. At the very least, he won’t be able to appear again anytime soon. If you’re going to search, then you should look around the northwest wall.”

“Understood. Thank you for the information. Oh, we’ve been chatting for a while now. Here, come this way. We’re almost there.” Liselotte directed them to a T-intersection down the corridor they were walking.

There wasn’t a sign of a single monster left inside the mansion, but just in case, small numbers of attendant girls were patrolling every area with knights in tow, strengthening the security in the area. And so, they passed many people on their way.

Liselotte stopped at the corner before they turned to the destination room and spoke to Flora in Rio’s arms. “Most regrettably, two knights have passed away. However, the hero, Lady Roanna, and Duke Huguenot are all safe. Please show them that you are as well.”

“Two... knights... I-I understand.” Two people had died because of her — Flora frowned in shame at that truth, but her dignity as a princess made her nod while biting her lip (incidentally, Flora was yet to be informed by Duke Huguenot that Alphonse and the knights dispatched to the forest had gone missing). Then, somewhat unconsciously, she tightened her clinging grip around Rio.

“...” A slightly uncomfortable expression showed on Rio’s face. Celia glanced at his side profile.

“Then please, come this way.” Liselotte began to move once more. She turned the corner and walked out into the corridor with the room where Roanna and the others were waiting.

The two knights guarding the outside of the open door immediately noticed Liselotte’s appearance. When they spotted Rio carrying Flora, they yelled into the living room in a hurry. “P-Princess Flora has returned!”

“I-Is that true?! Princess Flora? Princess Flora?!” Roanna came rushing out of the door in a panic. The normally-calm girl was terribly shaken at the moment, leaping through the door and looking around the corridor wildly. Then, when she spotted Flora being carried in Rio’s arms, she approached Flora on shaky legs.

“Oh, thank goodness, thank goodness you’re safe...!”

“Roanna...” Flora called Roanna’s name weakly.

“Are you... are you hurt anywhere, Princess Flora?! Please accept my utmost apologies. My thoughtless action led to Your Highness being placed in such terrible danger. Oh, however will I repent for this...” Roanna kneeled as soon as she reached Flora, lamenting with deep regret.

Flora shook her head with a fleeting smile. “It’s not your fault, Roanna. Sir Haruto saved me, so I’m fine. Are you all right yourself? You kept protecting me...”

“Of course! I am unscathed. Duke Huguenot suffered a deep wound, but his life is no longer in danger after healing. The hero is safe too.”

Flora smiled weakly. “I’m glad. But I heard there were knights that had passed away too...” she said, frowning regretfully.

“...Yes. The two who were originally guarding the outside of the door were killed... Umm, I understand how you must be feeling to a painful degree, but they died for the just cause of protecting Your Highness. If possible, please praise them as brave heroes.” Roanna chose her words carefully, as though to encourage Flora.

“...Right,” Flora bit her lip and nodded.

“But I’m truly, truly glad to see you’re safe, Princess Flora. If something unforgivable had been done to you, I... I... Oh, Sir Haruto, thank you. Thank you so much. I simply cannot thank you enough.” Roanna shuddered at the thought of what could have gone wrong and thanked Rio imploringly.

Rio shook his head gently. “No, it’s nothing to be thanked for. I’ll carry her inside the room, but please look after Princess Flora after that. She still seems to be frightened.”

“Of course. I will repay this debt in the future. Please, come this way,” Roanna nodded with determination before inviting them inside. Rio and the others proceeded to follow Roanna into the living room. Hiroaki was still lying unconscious, but the bodies of the two knights had been moved away somewhere.

When Rio entered the room, Duke Huguenot welcomed him and Flora with a powerful voice. “Ooh, Princess Flora! You’re safe...! Haruto, you have my gratitude!”

“Uh...” In contrast, Stewart averted his eyes from Rio awkwardly.

“It was nothing,” Rio said.

In the meantime, Roanna immediately prepared a chair for Flora to sit in. “Please, have a seat here.”

“I’m letting you down now. Excuse me.” This time, Rio made sure to put Flora down.

“...Okay. Thank you... very much,” Flora said with a somewhat reluctant face, then released her grip on Rio’s clothes. Even after being placed to sit in a chair, her gaze was locked on Rio’s face.

Rio felt awkward on the receiving end of Flora’s gaze. He looked at Celia and Aishia. “...I’m going to take my leave now. Shall we go?” he suggested now that their business was done.

“P-Please wait a moment. Where are you going?” Liselotte asked, stopping Rio in a hurry. She had received a report earlier that things had calmed down outside, so she was hoping to exchange a little more information with him.

“I’ll only be a bother if I remain here like this, so I was thinking of going outside to help,” Rio said while looking at Stewart.

He had just been in a dispute with him the other day. It was more than enough reason for the two of them to feel awkward about being in the same room as each other. That being said, his actual intention was to avoid Celia being in the same room as Beltrum’s royalty and nobility as much as possible.

Liselotte recalled the discord between them and immediately directed the conversation to their departure. “Oh, I do apologize. May I request that of you, then?” Normally she would have noticed much sooner and moved to separate them, but the emergency situation had prevented her from getting that far, much to her regret.

Gosh, I’m hopeless. I must be tired. She’d inform Duke Huguenot and the others of what had happened after the crisis passed instead. It wasn’t something she needed to prioritize at this moment.

“Leave it to me.” Rio placed his right hand against his chest respectfully.

“You should go too, Liselotte. We’ll get the details from Princess Flora,” Duke Huguenot urged.

“Thank you for the consideration. There’ll be a need to go over what is going on sooner or later, so I’ll arrange a meeting once the danger has passed. I’ve increased the security inside the mansion to the maximum, so please rest your body. I will also apologize for my failures on another occasion,” Liselotte spoke fluently, bowing her head.

Duke Huguenot smiled faintly. “There’s no need for you to worry. Pay us no mind and continue your direction over the situation. Haruto, allow me to thank you for saving Princess Flora on a later occasion.”

“Your words are enough for me,” Rio lowered his head respectfully.

“Umm, Sir Haruto!” Flora suddenly called out to Rio with all her might.

“...Yes?” Rio replied, turning his fixing gaze on Flora.

“Ah, umm... Thank you very much, for what happened. Could we please talk some more later?” Flora asked with a somewhat frightened expression.

“Of course. Now, if you would excuse me. Lady Liselotte,” Rio nodded respectfully with his right hand on his chest before looking at Liselotte.

“All right. I’m leaving the rest to you, Grace. You can give orders to the attendants and knights patrolling the area if you need anything,” Liselotte bowed her head deeply, then called out to the attendant girl waiting in the room.

“Yes, my lady!” Grace nodded humbly.

“Then, the three of you, come this way.” Liselotte led Rio and the others out of the living room.

◇　◇　◇

“Lady Liselotte, I’d like to return to the northwest area of the city to try and search for traces of the kidnappers. Would this be okay?” Rio asked once they’d left the living room with Flora and the others.

“Of course. There’s nothing more I could ask for if you’d investigate,” Liselotte agreed while examining Rio’s expression. With her hands full with dealing with the monsters and no personnel free to send, the offer was something Liselotte would have gladly bowed her head to request herself, so for Haruto to volunteer was perfect. It wasn’t a job to leave to an amateur, but she had no complaints if it was him.

“The kidnapper is someone of interest to me as well. I’ll go and check if there are any clues,” Rio declared firmly.

“Understood. I’m counting on you,” Liselotte nodded.

“Leave it to me. I’d like to ask the two of you to stay here and assist Lady Liselotte. The three of us will talk when I return,” Rio said to Celia and Aishia.

Celia suppressed her worries and smiled innocently. “...Okay. I’ll be waiting.”

“Thanks,” Rio nodded with a smile to reassure Celia.

“See you later. Leave Cecilia to me,” Aishia said, sending Rio off as she usually did.

“I’m counting on you, Aishia.” Rio smiled.

If anything happens, let me know through telepathy, he added through said method of communication.

Yup. We won’t be able to connect if you go too far, so be careful.

Rio and Aishia’s telepathy range was roughly a radius of one kilometer. While it was technically possible to communicate over one kilometer, the connection quality rapidly decreased after that point. The distance from Liselotte’s mansion to the area where Rio and Lucius fought was actually the limit for a clear telepathic connection.

Got it. If anything happens, prioritize the professor’s safety over anything else.

Yup, nodded Aishia.

“...I’ll be going then, Lady Liselotte. I intend on having a look around the west gate on my way back, so I’ll report to you later,” Rio said, having passed those instructions on to Aishia.

“Thank you very much. Please allow me to thank you officially on a later date.” Liselotte bowed her head deeply.

◇　◇　◇

Several minutes later, Rio left the mansion once again, heading for the outside of the walls to Amande’s northwest. The area where he had fought Lucius earlier was battered with violent scars from their fight. The remnants of their battle weren’t only visible by the naked eye, however.

There’s still a large amount of ode jumbled together. I won’t be able to investigate with spirit arts. When Rio felt the accumulated remnants of magical essence nearby, he sighed quietly. There was a spirit art that could detect other people’s essence by releasing one’s own essence into the area, but with this much of it around, there was no way it could detect anything effectively. And there were ways of completely suppressing essence anyway.

Which means I’ll have to look around myself. But before that... Rio immediately changed his thought process and headed to the place he had last seen Reiss holding Lucius.

The ground’s been completely gouged away. I guess he removed any traces of blood before leaving. But if he had to move while carrying Lucius, then there should be blood sprayed somewhere...

Rio touched his hand to the ground and checked for any stains of blood. Since Lucius had been bleeding profusely from his entire body, there had to be something left behind along the route they took. As long as he could find that, then he could follow those tracks.

Rio looked around for a while, but —

...There’s nothing.

There were no stains that resembled Lucius’ blood anywhere. At the very least, not within a 10 meter radius of the scene...

During their fight, Rio’s attention was directed to the attack from the sky for a single, mere instant, and the interception of dark and light had obstructed his vision. There weren’t many ways of disappearing so abruptly in that limited time period.

I don’t see any footsteps in the area either. Did they leave via the skies? Rio suddenly looked up. When Rio’s spirit arts collided with the breath in the sky, the surrounding skies had been shaken by violent shockwaves, but it wasn’t impossible for an experienced spirit arts user to fly through it.

...Was that man a spirit arts user too?

The possibility was there; the ball of light Reiss had conjured before leaving was created without a verbal spell. It hadn’t been created with magic, at least. However, if he had flown through the sky, that should have made the trail of bloodstains even more noticeable, yet there wasn’t a single trace of that.

Which means the remaining possibility is Transilio...

It was possible there was another method Rio hadn’t considered yet, but teleportation would explain everything else. Transilio was impossible to recreate with the modern sorcery of Strahl, but it was a different case when ancient artifacts were involved. However, ancient artifacts with some form of teleportation in them were hard to come by, and there weren’t many in circulation. It was hard to know if they existed at all.

At any rate, with no concrete evidence, Rio would have to withhold his judgment for the time being. Even if he could narrow things down, the mystery remained exactly that.

But they may have escaped through another method. I’ll look around the area some more.

Regardless of whether or not they used teleportation, the wound was fatal and required immediate treatment. If they were hidden nearby, then they shouldn’t have gone very far yet.

Thus, Rio first started walking towards the forest. However, after ten minutes of walking around, he hadn’t spotted any traces remaining.

Nothing in sight, huh. There were no signs of Lucius’ blood spilled anywhere, nor any signs of Reiss trampling the grass with his feet. The aftermath of the earlier battle had left the forest in a mess, making it hard to spot something, but Rio was certain he hadn’t missed anything.

...Don’t tell me they escaped into the city, Rio thought, looking around the city wall next. However, there were no signs there either, so he headed for the west gate for now.

“...Sir Haruto?” Aria appeared in a casual manner, dressed in her combat-use attendant uniform and equipped with her enchanted sword. Her eyes widened slightly when she spotted Rio.

“What are you doing here, Aria?” Rio’s eyes also widened.

“Things at the east gate have calmed down, so I was thinking of investigating the dragon-like creature that released that fiery breath. May I ask the same of you, Sir Haruto?”

“I received a request from Lady Liselotte to investigate the kidnapper,” Rio replied, his explanation brief.

“A kidnapper, you say?” The normally unexpressive Aria widened her eyes in great interest.

“Earlier, the mansion was attacked by monsters. In the midst of that chaos, Princess Flora was kidnapped.”

“...Princess Flora was kidnapped?” The unexpected information made Aria freeze, her voice showing a hint of doubt. Her reaction was understandable — Liselotte’s estate should have been the safest place in Amande.

“The extermination of the surging monsters has already been completed. Lady Liselotte wasn’t harmed in the slightest and I have already retrieved Princess Flora, so there is no need to worry in that regard.”

“...I cannot thank you enough.” Aria suddenly bowed her head toward Rio.

“It’s nothing worth thanking me for. I actually ended up fighting the kidnapper, but he managed to get away after I cornered him. Now that I’ve returned Princess Flora to the mansion, I’m back to search some more.”

“Is that so? In that case, the one who forced back the attack that came down from the sky was...”

“It was me. The culprit got away while I was leveraging a counterattack,” Rio said with a bitter smile.

“...I understand the situation now. If that is the case, then I shall assist in your investigation,” Aria offered.

“No, I’ve already finished my search. I was going to check on the state of the west gate before heading back to the mansion. Unfortunately, there were no traces left behind, so I do not believe the culprit is in the area.”

“Understood. Then I shall accompany you back to the mansion instead — that was my original intention. There are no problems at the west gate, so I believe it is fine if I continue with my mission and accompany you.” She still had many things she wanted to ask, but that would wait until they were on the move.

“I understand. Shall we go, then?” Rio asked.

“Yes,” Aria nodded her head respectfully.

◇　◇　◇

Rio and Aria ran through the city until they returned to Liselotte’s estate. Once they were within the grounds, they came across attendants Natalie and Cosette.

When Cosette realized it was Rio, she welcomed him with a beaming smile. “Sir Haruto, welcome.”

“Long time no see, you two,” Rio replied with a friendly smile.

“Thank you so much for what happened earlier, Sir Haruto,” Natalie thanked Rio politely.

“It was a truly wonderful fight to witness. Thanks to you, we were able to eliminate the monsters surging the east gate,” Cosette praised Rio with a grin.

“I’m glad to be of help. However, it seemed like some of the humanoid monsters got inside the city...” Rio said with a faint frown.

“The evacuation of the residents had already been completed, so thankfully nothing big came out of it. Also, I heard that you defeated several of the monsters that made it into the middle of the city too,” Natalie said, bowing in gratitude.

Rio smiled gently. “I’m glad to hear that.”

“Allow us to lead you to our master. Please, come this way,” Cosette said, taking the initiative to become Rio’s guide.

At that, Aria finally opened her mouth to declare her presence in exasperation. “You know, I’m here too...”

“Oh, if it isn’t Aria. Why are you with Sir Haruto?” Cosette asked her curtly.

“I was checking out the northwest city wall on my way back to the mansion when I bumped into him,” Aria replied with a small sigh.

“Ah, investigating the location of that breath attack.” Natalie inclined her head.

Cosette shot Aria a smug look before directing her question at Rio. “There’s no doubt that Sir Haruto was the one that forced it back, yes?”

“Ah...” Miharu was rendered speechless at Latifa’s confession.

“The Strahl region is human territory, so there are practically no communities like this village where people of different races live together. If there are, they’re slaves. There’s no place for us other than slavery.” Latifa continued on with a troubled look. “The nobles that owned me raised me as an assassin. They put a magic collar on me, to keep me from disobeying. That’s why, when I regained my memories of my past life, I had already killed people. After my memories awakened too, with these hands, I...”

Latifa’s body trembled a bit as she looked down at her hands. It must have been painful just to recall. It was a past she normally kept sealed deep within her memories.

“It’s okay, Latifa. If it hurts, you don’t have to force yourself to tell me.” Miharu approached Latifa and grabbed her hand. She spoke with a pained look in her eyes.

Latifa shook her head from side to side. “No, I need to do this... In order to ask you a question later. That’s why... You may not want to hear this, but I want you to. Is that okay?”

“...Yup.” Miharu frowned, nodding deeply.

“Thank you. As an assassin, I... I was controlled by the slavery collar, and told to kill Onii-chan like the others... That was what happened between me and Onii-chan, before we came to the village,” Latifa said shamefully, biting her lip as she stared at Miharu.

“...Latifa.” Tears gently fell from Miharu’s eyes. The story was just too much to bear.

“I pretended to collapse so that I could kill Onii-chan. But, there was no way I could win against Onii-chan, and I easily had the tables turned on me. I thought I would be killed, but I didn’t want to die, became scared, then completely threw a crying fit, at which Onii-chan knocked me out...” Latifa said bitterly. It really was a miserable recollection.

“Onii-chan didn’t kill me, though. Instead, he removed the collar that was controlling me. Then he brought me, who didn’t have a place in Strahl, who was nothing more than a burden, all the way to this village. He gave someone like me, who didn’t even have their own will, a chance to live an ordinary life,” Latifa continued in a quiet but firm voice.

“...” Miharu was overwhelmed and stood there in silence.

“I’ve caused Onii-chan a lot of trouble. I owe him so much, more than I can repay him in this lifetime. Onii-chan’s kind, so he’d deny all that, but that’s not true at all. That’s why I’ll spend my life returning this debt to Onii-chan. That’s what I think...” Latifa said, then paused.

“...You really love Haruto, after all,” Miharu said softly. It was clear as day that Latifa really loved Rio from their conversation just now. So clear, it was almost too bright to look at directly.

“Yup, that’s right. I love Onii-chan. I love him as my brother, and as a man. I fell in love with the same person twice.” Latifa nodded.

“I-I see...” For some reason, Miharu felt her chest clenching and made a pained face.

“That’s why, I think I get it. The reason why Sara and Orphia and Alma, why everyone loves him too... They still seem to feel guilty for how horribly they treated him over the misunderstanding when we first wandered into the village, but I can tell they love him.”

“...Right,” Miharu nodded with difficulty. Since they had been living together like a family, Miharu had somewhat realized that too.

“What about you, Miharu?” Latifa suddenly asked.

“...Huh?” For a moment, Miharu wasn’t sure what she was asking, her eyes widening. But she understood her meaning in no time and flinched in shock.

“Do you love Onii-chan too, Miharu? This is the condition I gave at the beginning. The question I wanted to ask you,” Latifa asked bluntly, staring at Miharu up close.

“Uh...” Miharu was unable to answer on the spot, a terribly hesitant look on her face.

“You don’t have to rush. I want to hear your true feelings,” Latifa said calmly.

“I... I had someone I loved when I was little.” Miharu slowly opened her mouth, thinking hard. “I probably loved that person just as much as you are currently in love. It was natural for the two of us to be together every day, and I thought it would only be natural for us to be together forever... Me, and my childhood friend. Aki was also there, and the three of us would play together,” she continued.

“Mhm...” Latifa nodded, urging Miharu to go on.

“But our time together didn’t continue on for very long. When I was seven, that boy had to move far away with his father, after his parents divorced. Only Aki and I were left. Aki was that boy’s little sister, you know. She’s grown to hate him now, but back then, she loved her brother. After her brother left her, she shut herself away in her room for days and cried,” Miharu said slowly, looking back on those times.

Latifa’s eyes had widened when she found out Aki hated Haruto, but she chose not to touch upon that and instead asked nervously about Miharu at the time. “...Did you cry, Miharu?”

“I was three years older than Aki. I say that to make myself sound cooler, but I cried too. I cried the whole day he moved,” Miharu answered with a bitter smile. “But, when we parted, he made a promise to me. That when he grew up, he’d come to get me. That’s why we should get married. Then we could always be together, he could always be by my side, and protect me with his life...” she said with a sad, faraway look.

“Miharu...” Latifa felt like her chest was about to rip apart. In the end, Haruto was still able to keep that promise, even now. He would protect Miharu with his life.

“I’m a simple person, so I was really happy and stopped crying because of that. I don’t know if I still love that person now that I’ve grown up, but my memories of that time are a precious treasure to me. That’s why... That’s why... I couldn’t imagine having that kind of relationship with another man until now. But...” Miharu said in embarrassment, frowning at the end.

“But?” Latifa gulped.

“...I don’t know. Something like this, I’ve never... While living with Haruto, I started overlapping his existence with the person I knew. I know that it’s the wrong thing to do — I keep telling myself that — but lately my feelings keep surging up. The timelines don’t match, though, so it couldn’t be possible.”

Around and around, in circles. Miharu’s thoughts and feelings were sucked into a cycle of negativity. Her face twisted in pain as she ducked her head, but after a while, she raised it again.

“The person I loved when I was young was named Amakawa Haruto. The same name as Haruto.” She stared at Latifa as she spoke quietly, as though seeking an answer.

“...Sorry. I know what it is you’re trying to ask. Even so, I can’t tell you anything about Onii-chan’s past life from my own mouth.” That was what she had promised, after all. Latifa shook her head apologetically.

“Yeah. I’m sorry too, for troubling you like this... The reason I haven’t asked Haruto myself is probably because I still haven’t reached my own answer yet. I’m too scared to make sure...” Miharu bit her lip out of shame.

“...That’s understandable. You’re an older sister to two, so you have to consider Aki and Masato.”

In reality, Miharu was in a position as the eldest where she always had to consider the other two, not just herself. However, the point that ultimately made Miharu hold her ground was the mismatched timelines. There was no way Amakawa Haruto could have been a university student, since he was a first year high schooler like her. That’s why, logically speaking, there was no way they could be the same person.

That was the binding spell. Because she understood there was a time discrepancy, Miharu was unconsciously afraid of confirming with Rio. She believed it wasn’t something she should confirm, having the vague feeling something would change if she did.

“...Yeah. I have to keep it together. For the sake of those two,” Miharu said to herself.

While it could be interpreted as a way of avoiding the problem with Rio, it was also true that she had to face the issue with Satsuki head-on too. If anything, in terms of urgency this was more important. After all, meeting Satsuki wasn’t just something that concerned Miharu; it would affect Aki and Masato greatly in the future too. Rio had prepared such an opportunity for them, so they couldn’t let that go to waste.

It was their own matter. They couldn’t just leave it to other people, and they couldn’t shove it all at Rio either. Miharu calmed down a little, forcing her miserable feelings into her chest.

“When I’m watching you, I think to myself that I have to try harder too. Thank you — for listening to my story, and for answering my question.” Latifa’s mouth relaxed into a smile as she thanked Miharu, glad that she had been able to have a frank conversation.

I don’t think this current state can continue, either, Latifa thought from deep inside her heart, though she couldn’t explain it logically. Now that she knew Miharu’s feelings were inclined towards Rio, she knew the problem between Rio and Miharu had to be solved before she could proudly face Rio herself. She couldn’t give Rio her all before that.

“Umm, is that all you wanted to ask of me?” Miharu asked nervously.

Latifa glanced at the entrance and smiled sadly. “Yup. I know what your feelings are now. Like I said at the beginning, you can’t tell anyone about what I told you, okay? Especially not Onii-chan.”

“Yup, I promise,” Miharu agreed, returning the smile gently.

“Let’s go, then,” Latifa said in a slightly louder voice, turning towards the door. It creaked slightly, moving faintly as though a wind had blown. On the other side was —

...Miharu. Is that true?

It was Aki. She had been searching for Miharu to discuss things with her when she found the two of them conversing outside the house and ended up eavesdropping. Aki ran into the house to avoid being caught.

“What’s the matter, Aki?” Upon running into the living room, Aki encountered Sara, whose eyes widened slightly.

“Ah, no, I was just walking a little, thinking it might help process my thoughts, or something...” Aki said, making up an excuse on the spot.

“Oh, I know that feeling. Sitting still doesn’t suit me either,” Sara agreed with a giggle. Just then, Miharu and Latifa came back inside.

“We’re back!” The moment Latifa entered the living room, she greeted Aki energetically.

“Welcome back. Wait, where did you go? What about Rio?”

“We were talking just outside of the house. Onii-chan went for a short walk outside. He said he was going to say hi to the neighbors. I’m sure he’ll be back soon.” Latifa answered Sara’s question in her usual tone.

“I see. Let’s have lunch as soon as Rio’s back, then. All the preparations are done.”

Latifa’s nose twitched as she sniffed, then she smiled with a giggle. “Yup! You made all kinds of food today. It smells great. The smell reached all the way outside the house, so I’m starving.”

“It... smelled? I could only tell once we got inside...” Miharu’s eyes widened in wonder.

“That’s because I’m a werefox! I’m super sensitive to smell.” Latifa puffed her chest up proudly.

“I see.” Miharu giggled in amusement. Latifa looked at Aki, who was standing still somewhat awkwardly, and called out to her gently in worry.

“Aki, are you okay? You don’t look too well...”

“N-No, I’m fine. There’s nothing wrong at all.” Aki shook her head awkwardly, her voice high-pitched.

◇　◇　◇

Shortly after that, Rio returned, and it was soon time for lunch. The dining table was packed with the feast that Orphia, Sara, and Alma had prepared, but the atmosphere in the room was a bit awkward. There were conversations happening, but it wasn’t as lively as it usually was.

Aki, Masato, and Miharu in particular had stiff expressions on their faces. The reason being, of course, was what Rio had outlined upon his return. Even the normally-boisterous Masato was thinking seriously about what their plan of action needed to be.

“By the way, Rio,” Orphia suddenly said.

“Yes?” Rio replied immediately, looking at her.

“What kind of person is the noble that’s bringing you to the banquet?”

While they may not be directly involved, it was still a person that Miharu and the others would be relying on. She figured it wouldn’t hurt to learn more about what kind of person they were.

With that, everyone’s attention gathered on Rio.

“Let’s see... As I said to the head elders before, she’s intelligent with a strong sense of duty. She was placed in charge of the city at a young age, and also operates a huge organization that she established herself. I believe no one is more befitting of being called ‘talented’ than her,” Rio explained.

“She’s a woman? I had assumed it would be a man...” Orphia blinked in surprise. The others also seemed to have the preconceived notion that the noble was a man, so they were all slightly taken aback.

“Yes, I believe she’s around Orphia’s age,” Rio confirmed calmly.

“The same as me?” Orphia murmured in awe.

“Haruto, is that person possibly Amande’s...” Miharu suddenly said. It seemed like she had someone in mind.

“Yes. She’s the governor of Amande and the president of the Ricca Guild too,” Rio confirmed.

“Huh? Wasn’t the Ricca Guild the place that sold the underwe... the swimsuits that we were trying to reproduce?” Orphia nearly said underwear, but corrected herself to swimsuit. The village was currently manufacturing experimental modern underwear and swimsuits based on what Miharu and the others brought to the village. Since there was an overwhelming number of opportunities to use underwear, Orphia had said underwear by reflex, but she apparently thought that word was a little embarrassing to say in front of Rio.

“Yup. Amande was a nearby city back when we lived in the Strahl region...” Miharu nodded, thinking hard. She knew that the Ricca Guild sold a lot of items that resembled modern Japanese products, so it was possible that the president, Liselotte, could also have been reincarnated like Rio...

Which meant Rio might have shared information about his previous life with Liselotte.

“You said that you saved Liselotte during some predicament, but what happened?” Alma asked out of curiosity.

“It’s a long story, but to summarize: there was a large-scale monster attack on Amande, and I cooperated with the extermination efforts,” Rio answered broadly.

“Did everything work out okay?” Miharu asked worriedly. She had never imagined such a thing would occur after they left Amande.

“Yes. I wouldn’t be here otherwise. Just to be safe, I had Aishia wait in a location away from Amande,” Rio replied with a smile.

“We don’t get monsters in this village, so it’s a little hard to imagine, but if Rio says it was large scale then there must have been an exceptional number of them,” Alma muttered.

Monsters seemed to live in areas close to human civilization, so there were barely any that took up residence in the Wilderness. Instead, all kinds of savage creatures ran rampant. She knew well how they could be threatening when they ganged up.

In the meantime, Sara’s interest as a warrior was piqued. “Could you tell us what battling monsters was like, if you don’t mind?”

Perhaps it was also because they were gathered for a meal where they were more taciturn than normal that she thought it was a good topic to go with.

Latifa raised her hand. “Ah! I want to hear about the circumstances under which Onii-chan and his teacher Celia lived together instead!” It was something that had bothered her ever since Rio returned to the village and casually mentioned they were cohabiting. Now that everyone was gathered together, she figured this was the perfect time to ask.

“Geez, Latifa, don’t interrupt other people while they’re speaking... Wait, living together! You’re right! Was it true you were living together?!” Sara tried to object to Latifa in exasperation when the topic of Rio cohabitating with Celia came up and she flipped sides instantly, her expression changing.

“Y-Yes. This is also a long story, but...” Rio was a little surprised, but he replied with a wince.

“How curious indeed, Sara,” Alma said with a giggle.

“Ah, no, that’s not...” As Sara had shown an excessive reaction already, she mumbled her words while blushing deeply. Orphia giggled as she watched Sara act in such a way.

“Hey hey, is she your local mistress, Onii-chan?” Latifa suddenly asked.

At that, the spirit folk looked surprised and coughed.

“...She’s not. Where did you learn such a word?” Rio must have felt a headache coming on, as he was pressing his head with his hand lightly.

“From Dominic,” Latifa revealed honestly.

“Got it. I’ll have a word with him the next time I see him,” Rio said with a sigh. He figured there was a need to emphasize not teaching Latifa strange things like that...

“Good grief, that old man... I shall scold him too. I’m sorry about him.” Alma felt ashamed of her own family and apologized to Rio with a dejected slump in her shoulders.

“Say, Onii-chan. How did you end up living together? She’s a noble lady, isn’t she?” Latifa was still curious and pouted her lips as she pressed Rio to talk. Sara and the other girls also seemed interested, staring at Rio closely.

“All right, I’ll tell you,” Rio nodded with a strained smile, explaining the series of events that led to Celia’s rescue.

◇　◇　◇

Later that night, Miharu called Aki and Masato to her room. The three of them sat in chairs around a small table.

“Have the two of you settled on your thoughts about the situation?” Miharu asked, immediately getting straight to business.

“...Yup,” Aki nodded.

“I’m still in the middle of thinking, but I want to hear your opinions too,” Masato said, scratching his head roughly.

“I see. Then let’s talk about it. Aki, could you start by telling us your thoughts?” Miharu asked.

“I... I want to return to Strahl. If there’s a chance that my brother is there and there’s a possibility that I can meet him... Then I want to attend the banquet,” Aki said seriously.

Miharu nodded. “I see... Then what about you, Masato?”

“The main issue stopping me is the possibility that we won’t be able to return here. Being with Haruto might mean he can teach me swordcraft, but... My first goal was to win once against Arslan...” Masato said, pondering to himself. “But we have to meet with Satsuki and my bro at some point, I guess. Well, it doesn’t feel great knowing we’ll be a burden, but I do want to go see them,” he added.

“Will we really be unable to return to this village? With my brother and Satsuki,” Aki muttered.

“Didn’t they say that the king wouldn’t approve of that? At the very least, Satsuki’s affiliated with the Galarc Kingdom now,” Masato repeated Rio’s words from earlier, stating the predicted outcome.

“But we don’t know how my brother and Satsuki feel about that.”

“That may be true, but isn’t that why we have to meet them to find out? Bro and Satsuki could have made close friends within the kingdom already, you know?” Whether they could or could not leave the kingdom aside, there was a possibility that they didn’t want to leave.

“That’s why I’m saying we should go see them and ask them directly. We also have to talk about whether we can return to Earth or not. That’s our problem, right?” Rather than have Rio act as an agent, there were things that could only be conveyed by the people involved.

“Mmgh, I see... But even supposing that Bro and Satsuki wanted to come to this village, and that we can return here too, are we even allowed to bring them along? Isn’t this place meant to be a secret? We made a promise.”

“That would... require consulting Rio and the elders...” Aki trailed off towards the end. She seemed to feel as though they had caused enough trouble for Rio and the village, so she had an uncomfortable look on her face.

Masato raised his hands in a gesture of surrender and looked to Miharu. “Mm... it’s no good. I still have no idea what to do at all. What do you think, Miharu?”

Aki’s gaze followed him to Miharu too. Miharu had been listening to the two of them talk in contemplative silence the entire time. “...I can understand both of your concerns. On top of all that, I want to follow Haruto.”

“Me too!” Aki chimed in.

“Wait, Aki. Let me continue.”

“O-Okay...” Aki was taken aback and nodded uncomfortably.

“Like Aki said, this is our problem. That’s why it isn’t something we should leave completely up to Haruto... It would be preferable to meet up directly and discuss things. Isn’t that right?”

“...Yeah,” Aki agreed fearfully.

“But, like Masato said, we’d most likely be burdens and get in the way. That’s why... This isn’t exactly a compromise, but I’m thinking I should represent the two of you and attend the night banquet with Haruto,” Miharu said.

“Then what about us...?” Aki asked worriedly.

“You’d stay back here at the village. If you insist, we can ask if you can come along to Strahl, but I’ll be the only one to attend the night banquet. I want you to wait with Ai-chan somewhere safe near the castle,” Miharu said, peering at Aki’s face.

“But that’s... That means that even if Masato and I follow you to Strahl, there’s a chance we won’t get to see Satsuki at all, doesn’t it?” Aki asked, looking terribly frustrated.

“...Yeah. Haruto said he would try bringing Satsuki out of the castle if possible, but that doesn’t guarantee that he will, just that the possibility is there. Of course, I’ll try discussing it with Satsuki too to see if we can get the two of you inside the castle, but that’s not guaranteed either,” Miharu explained to Aki honestly. “Do you still want to go to Strahl regardless of that, Aki?”

“Uh...” Aki was unable to respond straight away, a tearful expression on her face.

“What about you, Masato?” Miharu continued.

“I...” Masato hesitated with a sour expression.

“We don’t know what kind of position we’ll be placed in at the castle, so having the three of us present would be an even greater burden on Haruto, don’t you think? That’s why I want you to let me talk to Satsuki alone first.” That way, even if Miharu became unable to move in the castle, Aki and Masato could return to the village.

“...Miharu, you...” Aki suddenly raised her head, trying to say something with a look of deep thought.

“What is it, Aki?” Miharu looked back at Aki, listening in earnest.

“Miharu, you... Haruto...”

Do you like Haruto? Is it because you’ve overlapped Haruto with that man so much? Is that why you want to be beside Haruto?

That’s what Aki wanted to ask, but the words got stuck in her throat and her mouth wouldn’t move. Instead, a very sulky expression fell across her face and she pouted with tears in her eyes.

“...Say, Aki. I know you might find it hard to rely on me, but I’m your big sister too. We’re not related by blood, but I’ve grown up with you this whole time, so I believe we are. That’s why... If you think of me in the same way, could you leave this to me just this once?” Miharu asked with a troubled face. Aki bit her lip in frustration and suddenly stood up.

“...All right.” She hugged Miharu, burying her face into Miharu’s chest.

“Thanks, Aki. I’m sorry.” Miharu smiled gently and patted Aki’s back to comfort her.

“It’s okay. But I still want to go to Strahl. Even if I can’t see Satsuki or my brother this time, I want to be beside you.” Aki shook her head and tightened her hold around Miharu.

“Aki...” Naturally, Miharu hugged Aki back tighter too.

“...Umm, are the two of you forgetting me?” Masato seemed to feel uncomfortable at being forced to watch the display of their sisterly love, as he reinforced his presence with embarrassment.

“What? You were here?” Aki said to Masato, her eyes slightly puffy with tears.

“Uh, yeah, I was. From the very beginning,” Masato stressed.

“Hmm... So? What, do you want to be hugged by Miharu too? Gross. What a pervert.” Aki shot Masato an unamused look, trying to hide her embarrassment.

“Wha— No, that’s not it! I wasn’t thinking anything about how jealous I was or how soft they must be!” Masato denied with a red face.

Chapter 6: Chance Encounter

Fifteen days after Rio and the others departed from the spirit folk village...

The journey had progressed without any particular obstacles, allowing them to reach the Strahl region safely. It was thanks to Rio choosing a safer route, having traveled between the spirit folk village and the Strahl region numerous times now.

It was before noon; their current location was far above the easternmost area of the Galarc Kingdom, known as the Nephilim Mountains — the mountain range that separated the Strahl region from the Wilderness.

“The Strahl region is past here,” Rio informed the others.

“So this is...” There was still no sign of civilization, but Sara and the other spirit folk girls looked down at their first glance of the vast Strahl region in awe.

“...” Latifa also stared down at the view before them.

“Are you scared, Latifa?” Rio asked.

“Nope, because Onii-chan’s with me! I’m fine!” Latifa answered, tightly hugging Rio, who was still carrying her.

“I see. If you feel uneasy at all, you can rely on me and the people around you.”

“Yup!” Latifa replied obediently to Rio’s gentle words.

“We’ve come back again. To the Strahl region...” Aki must have been nervous, as she was looking downwards restlessly.

“I hope we can find Takahisa,” Miharu said, squeezing Aki’s hand.

“Yup. Please ask Satsuki everything on my behalf, Miharu,” Aki said with a nod, squeezing Miharu’s hand back.

“First, we have to head to Aishia. Now that we’ve come this far, we should arrive before sundown. I’ll continue leading the way like I have been, so follow me,” Rio called out to the group flying behind him.

“Okay!” Miharu and the others focused and nodded firmly.

◇　◇　◇

Several hours later, before sundown — exactly as planned...

Rio led the others to an area by the outskirts of the Galarc Kingdom’s capital.

“It should be near the rocks here...” Rio searched through his memory as he looked down at the rocky area down below.

Just like hiding a tree in a forest, he had placed the rock house by other rocks. He could already feel his connection to Aishia nearby, but all the boulders were making it hard to search. Welcome home, Haruto. The telepathic message suddenly echoed in Rio’s head.

Aishia, I’m home. Good timing — I was just having trouble locating the house. Can you lead me there? Rio smiled wryly. If they could communicate telepathically, Aishia must be very close by.

Yeah, I’m heading to you now.

Hm? ...Ah, there you are. Rio spotted the figured closing in on them from diagonally to the right and smiled. His eyes had been fixed downwards, so he was a little slow to notice.

“It’s Lady Aishia.” Sara and the others had also noticed her.

“Welcome back.” Aishia came to a stop before them in a flash, calling out to Rio and the group.

“Ai-chan... we’re back.” Seeing Aishia for the first time in a while had Miharu’s eyes tearing up.

“Welcome home, Miharu,” Aishia said.

“It’s been a long time, Lady Aishia,” Sara said respectfully.

“Long time no see, Aishia!” Latifa called out happily.

“Hello, everyone. Celia’s waiting, so let me lead you to the house first. This way,” Aishia said, turning to head back in the direction she came. The party followed behind her, soaring through the air. Less than a minute later —

“We’re here. Over there.” Aishia pointed below. There was the rock house, with Celia standing outside waving her arms.

“That woman must be Rio’s teacher,” Alma muttered quietly.

“I’m nervous, but I hope I can introduce myself properly and become friends!” Orphia said with enthusiasm.

“Agreed,” Alma nodded with a small smile. Before long, they were landing on the ground. As everyone set their feet down, Celia welcomed the party with a little bewilderment.

“T-That’s a lot of people...”

“I’m home, Professor.”

“Y-Yeah. Welcome home...” Celia replied fearfully. She first looked at Latifa being carried in a princess hold, then around at Miharu and Sara and the others.

There are so many cute girls... I wonder what their relationship is?! Celia was driven with the urge to ask Rio, but with so many fellow travelers present she couldn’t help but hesitate.

For the record, Sara and the others were currently using magic artifacts in the shape of necklaces to appear like humans, hiding their racial features like ears and tails so that Celia couldn’t see.

“...” Latifa and the others watched Celia in captivation.

“...She really is young.” Sara looked at the woman she had heard about in curious wonder.

“She’s about the same height as Aki and Latifa, or maybe a bit taller?” Orphia said, cocking her head.

“She’s a very beautiful person,” Alma murmured, staring fixedly at Celia.

“H-Hey, who are these people? The Miharu person is among them, right?” Celia asked hesitantly. She must have felt uncomfortable from all the attention.

“Yes. That’s correct, but I’m not sure where to begin explaining. Introductions are in order too, so how about we head inside first?” Rio suggested with a troubled look.

◇　◇　◇

The group then moved to the living room of the rock house.

“Shall we all have a seat? To make introductions easier, can you all sit in groups of where you came from? Professor, you can come sit next to me,” Rio said, then sat on the three-seater sofa with Celia.

“I’ll go pour the tea, then,” Aishia volunteered.

“Ah, I’ll help, Ai-chan,” Miharu immediately offered.

Orphia stepped up too. “I’ll help too...”

“It’s fine. I already know everyone here, so the two of you should stay.” Aishia shook her head before departing. At that, Miharu and Orphia quietly sat down.

“Let’s get straight to it with introductions and an explanation of what’s going on,” Rio began. He was the only one other than Aishia who knew everyone present, so he had to take the lead. “First of all, this is Professor Celia. She’s my former teacher.”

Celia bowed awkwardly. “Hello...” Having ran away from the Kingdom of Beltrum, she wasn’t sure where to start with her introduction.

“I’m sorry. I know this must be very sudden, but I’ve given them a simple explanation of your circumstances — but only as much as they need. They also have their own rather special circumstances and would never reveal your information to anyone else, which I can guarantee. They’ll explain their background after this, so could you introduce yourself first, Professor?” Rio said to Celia quietly, his tone apologetic. Meanwhile, Sara and the others watched him speak while feeling slightly nervous.

“...All right. It’s a promise, okay?” Celia looked over at the rather stiff-faced girls and agreed in exasperation.

“Umm, like Rio said, I’m his former teacher, Celia Claire,” she began courteously. “I’m actually a noble from the Kingdom of Beltrum, but certain circumstances placed me under the care of Rio right now. Have you heard about what happened already?” she asked Rio, wondering what they knew thus far.

“Yes, very briefly. I apologize,” Rio said awkwardly.

“There’s no need to apologize.” Celia shook her head with a strained smile. “I’ll show you what I really look like, then.” She untied her hair, then removed the necklace artifact that was changing the color of her hair, changing her hair from blonde to silver.

“Whoa...” Masato let slip a sound of awe, captivated by Celia.

“...” Miharu and the rest all looked at Celia’s change in wonderment.

“I’m glad. If I hurt you or miss any spots, just let me know.”

“Yup. By the way...” Sara opened her mouth to say something, making Celia tilt her head.

“Hmm, what is it?”

“Umm. You’ve known Rio for a long time now, right?” Sara asked, curious about Rio and Celia’s relationship. It was a little difficult to ask in front of Rio, but now was a suitable time.

“That’s right. There were a few years in between where we didn’t see each other at all, but I first met him when he was seven, and knew him for over five years after that, so you could say it’s been a while.” Celia paused in washing Sara’s tail to answer, smiling as she reflected on the memories.

“Over five years...” Sara’s eyes widened. In terms of duration of time together, it was much longer than the spirit folk had known him.

“Yes. Huh? What’s wrong, everyone? Why the sudden silence?” Celia noticed the sudden silence in the bathroom and looked around her. Everyone’s attention was completely fixed on Celia, their eyes filled with curiosity.

“Umm! I want to ask about that too! Please tell me more about the old Onii-chan!” Latifa said boldly.

“Fufu, sure. I want to know more about the Rio that everyone knows too. Let’s all talk about it together,” Celia giggled in response to Latifa.

“...Then, I will too.”

“Me too!”

Alma and Orphia offered to participate too. However, their voices echoed all over the bathroom, so there was no real point, as everyone could hear everything.

“Uh...” Miharu was about to raise her hand too, but found herself unable to muster her courage and timidly withdrew her hand. Aki watched her do so closely.

Meanwhile, Aishia was silently washing her hair.

“Then, a question! What kind of child was Onii-chan like?” Latifa asked.

“Let’s see... Not much different to now, I guess? From the first moment we met, he was a rather mature child...” Celia replied, looking back on the past with nostalgia.

“So that’s what he was like...” Latifa accepted this with great interest.

“Ah, but his demeanor’s grown a little sharper now, I guess? Like he’s grown from a boy to a man, or matured into an adult, if I had to say?” Celia added, cocking her head.

“Then it doesn’t sound like he’s very different from the Rio we know.” Sara smiled somewhat happily.

“Come to think of it, Rio went to a school for human nobility, right? Umm, I heard that he was placed on a wanted list after being dragged into a tangle with some nobles...” Alma recalled.

“Yes, so you’ve heard about that from Rio too. He was in a bit of a special position, being an orphan and all. He was used as a convenient scapegoat,” Celia said with a frown.

“Rio... was an orphan?” This was news to Sara and the others, whose eyes widened in shock. Miharu and Aki had also been listening closely, as their eyes were as wide as saucers.

“Eh, h-huh? Didn’t you know? You knew about the academy, so I assumed... I’m sorry, please pretend you didn’t hear that... well, I guess you can’t.” Celia tried to explain herself in a panic, but slumped her shoulders when she realized she had messed up. Meanwhile, Aishia finished washing off the soap from her hair and slowly stood up, approaching Celia.

“Haruto wasn’t hiding that on purpose or anything. He didn’t tell you himself, but that was because he wasn’t asked, so he didn’t answer. Anything he wouldn’t have wanted to be spread he would have informed you of in advance, so don’t worry about it.”

“Really?” Celia hesitantly tilted her head.

“Yup, I think so too. I knew that Onii-chan was an orphan as well, after all.” Latifa nodded.

“Is that so?” Sara asked Latifa in wonder.

“Yup, that’s why it’s fine.” Latifa gave a fleeting smile. Aishia then left them to enter the bathtub first.

“I see... But I’ll apologize to him later, just in case,” Celia sighed.

“Umm, I know I shouldn’t pry too deeply into Rio while he isn’t present, but he once stated that he wasn’t nobility. May I ask why he was attending a school for nobles?” Alma asked.

“...I can tell you the superficial truth. He saved a member of the royal family of my kingdom, so he was admitted into the academy as a reward. But with how he ultimately ended up being used as a scapegoat and was treated so coldly within the academy... it was more of a punishment than a reward,” Celia said uncomfortably.

“Was there nothing that could be done about the wanted notice?” Sara asked in frustration, unable to bear the thought of that.

“...I don’t think there was. It may sound like an excuse, but the one who made the decision was the king and an extremely small number of his nobles that controlled the kingdom. I was just a lecturer at the academy, nothing more than a researcher, so I had no real power at all. I only knew about the wanted notice by overhearing someone else, and by then it was already too late...” Celia said with an expression of deep shame and regret over her own powerlessness.

“I’m sorry for asking something so difficult to answer,” Sara apologized, her wolf ears and tail drooping.

“No no, it’s fine.” Celia shook her head weakly with a sad smile.

“Umm, then, can I ask one more question?” Orphia said, raising her hand.

“Of course,” Celia agreed readily.

“I’d like to ask about how you and Rio spent your time together within the academy. Rio seems really fond of you, so I assumed you must have had wonderful memories together,” Orphia said with a warm smile.

“How we spent our time... It was pretty normal, I think?” Celia tilted her head in slight embarrassment.

“I want to hear about that normal. I’m sure it was special to Rio, who was isolated from his surroundings at the time,” Orphia said, with Sara and Latifa nodding along.

“...Thank you for saying that.” Celia smiled happily.

“So what did you do specifically?” Sara had forgotten her tail was being washed as she turned around to ask Celia directly.

“L-Let’s see. There were eyes everywhere within the academy, so we spent a lot of time meeting in my research lab. We used to drink tea together often there. We would chat about things, and he’d also help with my research...” Celia looked back on the past with a smile at her lips.

“I see. So to Onii-chan, his time with Celia was his healing time.” Latifa crossed her arms and grunted in understanding. She had actually heard about Celia from Rio personally several times before, but her awareness of her as a rival was newly refreshed.

“That... might be true. I’d be happy if it was.” Celia grinned shyly.

“I’m sure it was. Right, Aishia?” Latifa nodded firmly and addressed Aishia, who was soaking in the water with Miharu and Aki. Miharu also looked over at Aishia in interest.

“Yup,” Aishia said quietly.

“See!” Latifa gave a sunny and cheerful smile.

“Thank you,” Celia said bashfully.

“I’ve said this before, but the reason why Haruto is able to open his heart to people now is because of how Celia treated him while he went to the academy. It’s because Celia was always by Haruto’s side when he was at his loneliest that Haruto didn’t completely shut out others.” Aishia had a rare smile on her face as she added to her words eloquently. If he hadn’t had anyone he could talk to for over five years, he would have definitely stopped trusting people entirely.

“T-That’s an exaggeration.” Celia felt helplessly awkward, being praised so openly in front of everyone.

“Nope, I think Aishia’s right. It’s thanks to you being there that we were able to grow close to Onii-chan. Thank you very much,” Latifa said, bowing to Celia.

“...Thank you,” Sara and the others exchanged a look before bowing their heads at Celia with a giggle.

“Hey, don’t make fun of me!” Celia’s face reddened.

“But...” Miharu, who had been listening silently until now, opened her mouth for the first time. Everyone’s attention gathered on her.

“But I think that’s the truth. Because he’s so kind,” Miharu said with a slightly high-pitched voice. That was all she wanted to say, yet her chest was thumping uncontrollably, and she clenched her fists before her chest.

“...Thank you. That might be right. He might be cowardly and awkward, but there’s no mistaking the fact that he’s a kind person.” Celia’s eyes widened, her tone softening as she spoke.

“Cowardly, you say?” Sara asked hesitantly.

“Yup. He’s a little distrustful of other people, or maybe you could call it being extremely wary about things. That’s why he’s a coward. Aishia was the one that said it though, I just applied my own reasoning to it,” Celia said with a faint smile.

“...What about awkward and kind?” Alma asked curiously.

“Hmm... It’s like he doesn’t doubt the people he trusts, and will believe them to the end, you know? He once said so himself that he was distrustful of other people, but I don’t think he actually wants to doubt them. That’s why he’s awkward, but kind.” Celia seemed to be having fun talking about Rio to others, as her thoughts came out as words quite fluently.

“...You sure understand Rio well.” The spirit folk girls were in awe, watching Celia with looks of respect. Meanwhile, Miharu was watching Celia with a half-envious, half-awed look. Aki, in turn, was observing on her.

“A-Ahaha, well, I have been close to him ever since he was in school.” Celia seemed to be embarrassed, as she tried to brush it off with a laugh.

“Yup, I got it! In other words, you like Onii-chan, right?” Latifa suddenly exclaimed after quietly listening to Celia speak.

“Um... W-Why would you think that?!” Celia was taken aback, shouting as her face turned bright red.

“Eh? Because you really understand Onii-chan.” Latifa tilted her head.

“T-That’s because... I’m his teacher and he’s my student!” Celia explained in a high-pitched voice.

“Hmm, I wonder if that’s true... But you asked Onii-chan to help you run away from your wedding ceremony, right? I want to hear a little more about that. Right, everyone?” Latifa turned a dubious look at Celia, but continued with a question for Sara and the others.

“Ah...” That reminded them of the story behind Celia and her wedding.

“Come to think of it, that’s right. We wanted to hear more details about that from you too.” Sara nodded.

“E-Eeh? B-But I’m still in the middle of washing your tail, so how about I finish this first so we can sit in the bath? You might catch a cold like this.” Celia hesitated, trying to avoid the topic, but it was clear that all further questions for her would surround said topic.

In the end, they ended up having a fairly long bath together, chatting and having fun. There was a slight dispute over room allocations once they got out of the bath and had to go to bed, but that is a story for another time.